{
  "quiz": {
    "questionItem": [
      {
        "question": "What is the previous version of HTML, prior to HTML5?",
        "panswer": [
          "HTML 4.1",
          "HTML 4",
          "HTML 4.01",
          "HTML 4.9"
        ],
        "aanswer": "HTML 4.01"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which doctype is correct for HTML5?",
        "panswer": [
          "!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC '-//W3C//DTD HTML 5.0//EN' 'http://www.w3.org/TR/html5/strict.dtd'",
          "!DOCTYPE HTML5",
          "!DOCTYPE html",
          "!DOCTYPE html5.0"
        ],
        "aanswer": "!DOCTYPE html"
      },
      {
        "question": "In HTML5, which element is used to group heading elements?",
        "panswer": [
          "hgroup",
          "group",
          "headings",
          "header"
        ],
        "aanswer": "header"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following elements is no longer supported in HTML5?",
        "panswer": [
          "q",
          "menu",
          "font",
          "ins"
        ],
        "aanswer": "font"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following elements is no longer supported in HTML5?",
        "panswer": [
          "base",
          "cite",
          "acronym",
          "abbr"
        ],
        "aanswer": "acronym"
      },
      {
        "question": "In HTML5, onblur and onfocus are:",
        "panswer": [
          "Style attributes",
          "HTML elements",
          "Event attributes",
          "Element attributes"
        ],
        "aanswer": "Event attributes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct HTML5 element for playing video files?",
        "panswer": [
          "media",
          "video",
          "movie",
          "mpeg4"
        ],
        "aanswer": "video"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct HTML5 element for playing audio files?",
        "panswer": [
          "mp3",
          "sound",
          "audio",
          "wav"
        ],
        "aanswer": "audio"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which attribute for 'script' elements is no longer required in HTML5?",
        "panswer": [
          "src",
          "type",
          "href",
          "rel"
        ],
        "aanswer": "type"
      },
      {
        "question": "In HTML5, which method is used to get the current location of a user?",
        "panswer": [
          "getPosition()",
          "getCurrentPosition()",
          "getUserPosition()",
          "getCoordinates()"
        ],
        "aanswer": "getCurrentPosition()"
      },
      {
        "question": "The new HTML5 global attribute, 'contenteditable' is used to:",
        "panswer": [
          "Update content from the server",
          "Specifies a context menu for an element. The menu appears when a user right-clicks on the element",
          "Return the position of the first found occurrence of content inside a string",
          "Specify whether the content of an element should be editable or not"
        ],
        "aanswer": "Specify whether the content of an element should be editable or not"
      },
      {
        "question": "In HTML5, contextmenu and spellcheck are:",
        "panswer": [
          "Event attributes",
          "HTML elements",
          "HTML attributes",
          "Style attributes"
        ],
        "aanswer": "HTML attributes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Graphics defined by SVG is in which format?",
        "panswer": [
          "HTML",
          "CSS",
          "XML",
          "JSON"
        ],
        "aanswer": "CSS"
      },
      {
        "question": "The 'canvas' element in HTML5 is used to:",
        "panswer": [
          "create draggable elements",
          "draw graphics",
          "manipulate data in MySQL",
          "display database records"
        ],
        "aanswer": "draw graphics"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which built-in HTML5 object is used to draw on the canvas?",
        "panswer": [
          "getContent",
          "getCanvas",
          "getContext",
          "getGraphics"
        ],
        "aanswer": "getContext"
      },
      {
        "question": "In HTML5, which attribute is used to specify that an input field must be filled out?",
        "panswer": [
          "required",
          "formvalidate",
          "validate",
          "placeholder"
        ],
        "aanswer": "required"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which input type defines a slider control?",
        "panswer": [
          "slider",
          "controls",
          "search",
          "range"
        ],
        "aanswer": "range"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which input type defines a week and year control (no time zone)?",
        "panswer": [
          "week",
          "date",
          "year",
          "month"
        ],
        "aanswer": "week"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which HTML5 element is used to display a scalar measurement within a known range?",
        "panswer": [
          "range",
          "gauge",
          "meter",
          "measure"
        ],
        "aanswer": "meter"
      }
    ]
  }
}